Guide to the Brooklyn Arts Council Folk Arts collection CBHM.0002
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 1: Early Programs
  - Sub-series 1.1: Program Files
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Flyers and Brochure, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Press Releases, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Publicity, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Video Log, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Storytelling Tent, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Flyers and Brochure, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Publicity, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Internal, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Contracts, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Field Notes, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Publicity, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Participant, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Contracts, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Press Releases, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Publicity, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Storytelling Tent, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Contracts, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Publicity, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Press Releases, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Budget, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Storytelling Tent, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Budget, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Release Form, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Press Releases, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Storytelling Tent, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Publicity, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Prospect Park Alliance Collaboration, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Related Activities, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Press Releases, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Storytelling Tent, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Certificates, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Brooklyn Public Library, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Fieldwork, Logs, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Response Sheets, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Publicity, Clippings, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Flyers, Brochures, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Contracts, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Release Forms, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Publicity, Press Contracts, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Brochure, Production, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Storytelling Tent, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Storytelling Tent, Release Forms, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Brochure and Flyers, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Press Releases, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Contracts, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Fieldwork, Data Sheets, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Funding, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Local Celebrations, Events, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Notes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Photographs, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Storytelling Tent, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Contracts, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Fieldwork, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Welcome Back to Brooklyn, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Praise in the Park, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      General
      For additional materials see Series XI: Praise in the Park: Musical Expressions of Faith
    - Photographs, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Misc., 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Folk Arts in Education, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Artist File: Cheryl Byron and Something Positive, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Artist File: Patricia Dye and Paka, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Artist File: Donny Golden, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Artist File: Guillermo Guerreo, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Artist File: Chief Isaac Komolafe, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Artist File: Trilok Fusion and Sudha Seetharaman, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Artist File: Tamara Volskaya and Anatoliy Trofimov, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Artist File: La Troupe Makandal, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Archives, 1995-2011 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Copyright, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Lefferts Homestead Collaboration, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - NYYCA Folk Arts Roundtable, 1989-1997 (Box 5, Folder 22-25)
    - Volunteers, circa 1988 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - African, 1989-1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - African American, Gospel Music, 1988-1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - African American, Valerie Bailey and Quilters, circa 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Caribbean, Afro-Cuban, circa 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Caribbean, Cuban, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Caribbean, Dominican, 1990-1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Caribbean, Guyanese, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Caribbean, Haitian, 1985-1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Caribbean, Indo-Caribbean, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Caribbean, Jamaican, 1988-1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Caribbean, Puerto Rican, Adrian Garcia, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Caribbean, Puerto Rico, Jose Aviles, 1989-1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Caribbean, Puerto Rico, Los Pleneros de la 21, 1984-1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Caribbean, Puerto Rican, Misc., 1987-1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Caribbean, West Indian / Trinidadian, 1975-1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Indigenous, 1989-1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Panamanian, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - NEA, Folk Arts Series, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - NEA, Folk Arts Series, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - NEA, Jewish Folk Arts, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - NEA, Our Daily Bread, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - NEA, Folk Arts Series, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - NEA, Our Daily Bread, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - NEA, Folk Arts Series, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - NEA, Folk Arts Series, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - NEA, Folk Arts, Brooklyn Children's Museum Partnership, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - NEA, Folk Arts, Brooklyn College Collaboration, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - NYSCA, Adopt-A-Landmark, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - NYSCA, Presentation, Fold Arts Series, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - NYSCA, Consultation, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - NYSCA, Folk Arts Series, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - NYSCA, Welcome Back to Brooklyn, Storytelling, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - NYSCA, Staff Folklorist, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - NYSCA, Summary Report, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - NYSCA, Folk Arts Series, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - NYSCA, Staff Folklorist, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - NYSCA, Welcome Back to Brooklyn, Storytelling Tent, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - NYSCA, Our Daily Bread, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - NYSCA, Administrative and Program Costs, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - NYSCA, Programming, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - NYSCA, Programming, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - NYSCA, Programming, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - NYSCA, Programming, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - NYSCA, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - NYSCA, Programming, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Fundraising, Project One City, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Fundraising, Grant Proposals, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Fundraising, United Way of New York City, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Fundraising, ITVS, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Fundraising, Arts Partners, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Fundraising, Lila Wallace, Readers Digest Community Folklife Program, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Fundraising, Chemical Bank, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Fundraising, Lila Wallace, Readers Digest Community Folklife Program, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Fundraising, Lila Wallace, Readers Digest Community Folklife Program, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Cathy Ragland Files, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Welcome Back to Brooklyn, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Folk Arts Sampler, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Folk Arts in the Library, 2000-2001 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - BAC Professional Development, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - BACA Contracts, RESTRICTED, 1987-1997 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      Due to sensitive personal information, these materials are not open for research.
  - Sub-series 1.2: Audiovisual
    A partial cassette inventory is included in Box 8 and a partial VHS inventory is included in Box 14.
    - Audio, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Item 1-37)
    - Audio, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Item 1-32)
    - Audio, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Item 1-34)
    - Audio, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Item 1-34)
    - Audio, 1993-1997 (Box 12, Item 1-36)
    - Audio, circa 1986-1997 (Box 13, Item 1-35)
    - Audio and Video, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Item 1-25)
    - Video, 1989-2000 (Box 15, Item 1-15)
    - Video, 1996 (Box 16, Item 1-14)
    - Video, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Item 1-14)
    - Audio and Video, Master Audio Tapes, circa 1991-1996 (Box 18, Item 1-20)
    - Audio, circa 1993 (Box 18, Item 1-4)
    - Master Audio Tapes, 1996 (Box 18, Item 1-4)
    - Master Audio Tapes, 1996 (Box 19, Reel 5-18)
    - Brooklyn Storytelling Tent, Negatives and Contact Sheets, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Storytelling Tent, Prints, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Folk Arts and Artists, Negatives and Contact Sheets, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Fieldwork, Negatives and Prints, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Artists and Musicians, Prints, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn Storytelling Tent, Negatives and Contact Sheets, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Welcome Back to Brooklyn, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn Folk Arts and Artists, Negatives and Contact Sheets, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Folk Art and Artists, Slides, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Binder 1)
    - Folk Art and Artists, Slides, 1990 (Box 21, Binder 2)
    - Folk Art and Artists, Slides, 1990 (Box 21, Binder 3)
    - Folk Art and Artists, Slides, 1991 (Box 22, Binder 4)
    - Folk Art and Artists, Slides, 1992 (Box 22, Binder 5)
    - Folk Art and Artists, Slides, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Binder 6)
    - Folk Art and Artists, Slides, 1995, 1997 (Box 23, Binder 7)
    - Folk Art and Artists, Slides, 1996 (Box 23, Binder 8)
    - Folk Art and Artists, Slides, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Binder 9)
    - Program Photographs, 1998 (Box 24, Binder 1)
    - Program Photographs, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Binder 2)
    - Program Photographs, 1996-2000 (Box 24, Binder 3)
    - Artist Provided Media, Video, circa 1997-1998 (Box 102, Item 1-9)
    - Artist Provided Media, Audio, circa 1997-1998 (Box 102, Item 10-22)
    - Artist Provided Media, Video, circa 1994-2003 (Box 103, Item 1-10)
    - Artist Provided Media, Audio, circa 1998-2001 (Box 103, Item 11-14)
    - Research Materials, Video, circa 2000-2005 (Box 104, Item 1-9)
    - Research Materials, Audio, circa 2001 (Box 104, Item 10-14)
    - Various Media, Video, circa 2005-2014 (Box 105, Item 1-3)
    - Various Media, Audio, circa 1995-2012 (Box 105, Item 4-66)
- Series 2: Black Brooklyn Renaissance
  Historical Note
  Black Brooklyn Renaissance: Black Arts + Culture 1960-2010 (BBR) was developed and presented by Kay Turner, Folk Arts Director at the Brooklyn Arts Council. BBR was a two year-long research, planning, and public presentation initiative in partnership with Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation. Beginning research in 2009 with major programming presented in 2010, BBR culminated in February 2011. Through field research, a series of public performances, exhibitions, panels and workshops, a scholarly conference, an oral history project, and other documentation, BBR celebrated the many ways Black performing artists, primarily those working in music, dance and spoken word, have contributed to the borough's significance as a center of Black culture in New York and the world.
  BBR's yearlong programming was held at major venues and community sites throughout Brooklyn, with select programs in Manhattan. Many of BBR's concerts, panels and workshops examined how migration, immigration, and political movements galvanized these cultural expressions while drawing attention to the evolving interplay between Afro-Caribbean, southern African American, and African traditions. The project also sought to create a dialogue between young contemporary artists and leading artists of the 1960s, '70s and '80s. Black Brooklyn artists of different generations and styles shared, learned and performed together.
  Program Files include information on the development and planning of Black Brooklyn Renaissance, including meeting notes, promotional materials, funding information, budgeting, and correspondence. Program Files also include a large group of folders relating to artists who were involved in the Black Brooklyn Renaissance project. Contents include permission statements for audiovisual recordings, tape logs highlighting recorded interviews or performances, biographical information, performance information, and performance CDs. Folders labeled "context" includes materials collected during the planning and the run of the Black Brooklyn Renaissance to show the program's cultural context, events that were related to but not part of BBR.
  Audiovisual items include digital photographs, audio, and video documentation of the various events that comprised the Black Brooklyn Renaissance program. Also included are additional interviews with individuals involved in the community and in the various arts represented in the programs. Most of the items in this series are compact discs.
  A Digital Archive containing 73 compact discs was produced and given to 6 repositories, including the Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture and the American Folklife Center at the Library of Congress. The archive includes over 100 interviews with artists and community leaders, event recordings, concerts, and panel discussions. The folders in box 26 contain material relating to the production of the archive, its dissemination, and the release and reception for its debut in February 2012. The Digital Archive itself, as packaged for dissemination to the various repositories is box 37.
  Black Brooklyn Renaissance Events:
  Kumau Brathwaite at the 10th National Black Writers'. Founders Auditorium, Medgar Evars College, 1650 Bedford Ave. Presented by the National Black Writers' Conference with support from BAC, March 25, 2010.
  Cal Massey Jazz Tribute. Gershwin Hall, Brooklyn Center for the Performing Arts and Brooklyn College (BCBC). Presented by the H. Wiley Hitchcock Institute for Studies in American Music at Brooklyn College and Central Brooklyn Jazz Consortium with support from BAC, April 22, 2010.
  Jazz Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony. Brooklyn Historical Society. Presented by BHS in conjunction with Central Brooklyn Jazz Consortium's 11th Annual Central Brooklyn Jazz Festival, April 29, 2010.
  Recording Brooklyn. Presented by PAC as part of its Scene: Brooklyn Independent Film and Media Arts series in conjunction with the Brooklyn Chapter of the Links, undated.
  Foly: African Dance Master Classes. Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation,1638 Fulton Street. Presented by Bed Stuy Restoration Corp with support from BAC, May 14-15, 2010.
  Lions Will Roar, Swans Will Fly, Angels Will Wrestle Heaven, Rain Will Break: Gukurahundi. The Kumble Theater for the Performing Arts, Long Island University. Presented by 651 Arts in association with Dance Theater Workshop, with additional support from BAC and funding from American Express, May 21-22, 2010.
  Juneteenth Celebration at 227 Abolitionist Place, 227 Duffield Street, presented by Friends of 227 Abolitionist Place with support from BAC, June 19, 2010.
  39th International African Arts Festival (IAAF), Commodore Barry Park, presented by IAAF with support from BAC, July 2-5, 2010.
  Emancipation Day Celebration at Weeksville Heritage Center 1698 Bergen Street, presented by Weeksville Heritage Center with support from BAC, July 3, 2010.
  Eyewitness: Beautiful Black Brooklyn (photo exhibition). Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Center for Arts and Culture, Skylight Gallery. Presented by Skylight Gallery with support from BAC, July 10-September 30, 2010.
  Brooklyn Transformation (Outdoor Film Screening), Fort Greene Park. Presented by Rooftop Films in cooperation with BAC's Scene: Brooklyn program, July 17, 2010.
  Lincoln Center Out of Doors Presents The Robert Glasper Experiment with Special Guests Q-Tip and Bilal Jose James' Blackmagic, Damrosh Park Bandshell, Lincoln Center, August 4, 2010.
  Carnival Masqueraders in Brooklyn, exhibition at Skylight Gallery, Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, presented by Skylight Gallery with support from BAC, October 2, 2010-January 5, 2011.
  Workshop: Learning to Listen to Gospel Music, BAC Gallery, November 4, 2010.
  African Dance/Brooklyn Style. Walt Whitman Theater, Brooklyn Center for the Performing Arts and Brooklyn College (BCBC), February 28, 2010.
  African Dance/Brooklyn Style Symposium. A.R.T./New York South Oxford Space, 138 S. Oxford Street. Presented by BAC and hosted by Urban Bush Women, March 3, 2010.
  Rites and Ceremonies of the Brooklyn African Diaspora. Brooklyn Historical Society, 128 Pierrepont Street. Presented by BAC in conjunction with BHS, March 17, 2010.
  Icons of Brooklyn Jazz. Sugar Hill Restaurant, 615 DeKalb Ave. Presented by Brooklyn Central Jazz Consortium with support from BAC and American Express, April 7, 2010.
  Hip Hop Hybrids of Brooklyn. Public assembly, 70 North 6th Street, Williamsburg. Presented by BAC with support from American Express, April 15 and May 22, 2010.
  Black Brooklyn Drum Call. Drumming demonstration and performances on the plaza; drum-making demo in the 2nd floor meeting room. Brooklyn Public Library, Grand Army Plaza, June 5, 2010.
  21st Annual Tribute to Our Ancestors of the Middle Passage. Ancestor circle, 16th Street and Coney Island Boardwalk. Presented with The People of the Sun Middle Passage Collective and Medgar Evars College with support from BAC, June 12, 2010.
  Preserving the Parade: Documenting the West Indian American Labor Day Carnival. Brooklyn Public Library, Flatbush Branch, June 17, 2010.
  Intergenerations: Toshi Reagon and Friends. Southpaw, 125 Fifth Avenue. Presented by BAC with support from American Express and Emma A. Shaefer Charitable Trust, July 29, 2010.
  J'Ouvert, West Indian Labor Day Parade, September 2010.
  Otto Neals and Emmett Wigglesworth: Kindred Spirits Forging Forward. Exhibition in the BAC gallery. September 24, 2010-January 14, 2011.
  Intergenerations: Dance Kings of Black Brooklyn. Kumble Theater for the Performing Arts, Long Island University, presented by BAC in cooperation with the Kumble Theater, October 9, 2011.
  The Black Brooklyn Renaissance Conference and Concert. Woody Tanger Auditorium, Brooklyn College. Presented by BAC and the H. Wiley Hitchcock Institute for Studies in American Music at Brooklyn College with support from the NY Council on the Humanities and Eleanor Archie, October 23, 2010.
  Brooklyn: The Gospel Borough. Memorial Hall, Concord Baptist Church of Christ, November 12, 2010.
  Word is Brooklyn. BAM Cafe, presented by BAC in cooperation with City Lore, November 19, 2010.
  The Brooklyn School of Black Visual Artists. Panel discussion, Artcurian, presented by BAC in conjunction with MoCADA and Artcurian, November 21, 2010.
  Intergenerations: Randy Weston Trio with Special Guest Ayanda Clarke. Brooklyn Museum, Cantor Auditorium, co-presented by the Brooklyn Museum and BAC, December 12, 2010.
  Voices of the Elders. Reception, interviews and panel discussion. Long Island University. Presented by BAC in cooperation with Ifetayo Cultural Arts Academy, Januray 30, 2011.
  Amateur Night at the Apollo: Brooklyn Night. Sponsored by the Coca-Cola Company, February 9, 2011.
  Black Brooklyn Renaissance: The New Generation. Project finale, BAM Cafe, co-presented by BAC and BAM Cafe live, February 11-12, 2011.
  Certain participants in Black Brooklyn Renaissance: Black Arts and Culture 1960-2010 have not granted permission for their likeness to appear in any related media. See box 28, folder 1 for a full list. Items in box 98, folder 11 are not open for research due to sensitive personal information.
  - Sub-series 2.1: Program Files
    - Project Description, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Calendars, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Meetings, BBR Staff and Presenters, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Meeting Notes, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Notes, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Contacts, Art, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Contacts Carnival, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Contacts, Dance, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Contacts, Lists, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Contacts, Misc., 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Contacts, Music, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - VIP Invitations to Kick-Off, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Calendars, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Community Calendars, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Photos for Possible Use, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Press Coverage, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Press/Marketing Misc., 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Press Releases, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Funding, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - American Express, Final Report, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Brooklyn Community Foundation, Final Report, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Franklin A. Thomas, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Met Life Foundation, Final Report, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Profit and Loss Detail, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Budget Planning and Notes, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Invoices and Check Requests, Archive, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Invoices and Check Requests, By Event, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 4-5)
    - Invoices and Check Requests, Misc., 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Invoices and Check Requests, Printing, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Invoices and Check Requests, Production, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Invoices and Check Requests, Programs (Artist Fees), Empty, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Invoices and Check Requests, RESTRICTED, 2010-2011 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Expenses, Misc., 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Archive Production, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Archive, Recipient Institutions, 2010-2011 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Archive, Release and Reception, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - BBR Introduction, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - African Dance / Brooklyn Style, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - African Dance / Brooklyn Style Symposium, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Rites and Ceremonies of the Brooklyn African Diaspora, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Kaman Braithwaite at the 10th National Black Writers Conference, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Hip Hop Hybrids of Brooklyn, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Celebrating Cal Massey, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Making Do the Right Thing, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - BAM Dance Africa Pre-Opening Activities-Weeksville, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Black Brooklyn Drum Call, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - 21st Annual Tribute to Our Ancestors of the Middle Passage, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Preserving the Parade: Documenting the West Indian American Labor Day Carnival, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Black Woman Voices, Tushi Reagon, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 13)